{
    "subject": "resource/Evangelos_Venizelos",
    "predicate": "ontology/primeMinister",
    "object": "resource/Lucas_Papademos",
    "human_readable": "Evangelos Venizelos was the Prime Minister of Lucas Papademos.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9244499802589417,
            "question": "Was Evangelos Venizelos a Prime Minister?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9108360409736633,
            "question": "Who was the Prime Minister of Lucas Papademos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8849229216575623,
            "question": "What role did Evangelos Venizelos hold in relation to Lucas Papademos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080572485923767,
            "question": "What is the significance of the relationship between Evangelos Venizelos and Lucas Papademos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7477948665618896,
            "question": "Who held the position of Prime Minister before Lucas Papademos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3223341703414917,
            "question": "Can you name any other positions held by Evangelos Venizelos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03584207594394684,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with this political relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02067636325955391,
            "question": "How is this relationship viewed by historians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.018231287598609924,
            "question": "What can we learn about Greek politics from this relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.015484881587326527,
            "question": "Were there any significant policies implemented during their time in office?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Evangelos Venizelos was the Prime Minister of Lucas Papademos.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4919_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we learn about Greek politics from this relationship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4919_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is this relationship viewed by historians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4919_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical events associated with this political relationship?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4919_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4919_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the format you requested:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information indicating that Evangelos Venizelos was the Prime Minister of Lucas Papademos. Instead, it is stated that Lucas Papademos became the newly inaugurated Prime Minister of Greece, and Evangelos Venizelos was named as the new finance minister under his government."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Evangelos Venizelos was appointed as the finance minister by Prime Minister George Papandreou, not by Lucas Papademos.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}